Barbara Dane collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Unidentified Sing-Out program with, AFC 1980/001: SR109; RWC 6440; 1 audiotape reel, 10 in.
    Sing-Out WBAI Barbara Dane and Irving Silber contents of this show unknown as box mangled by P.O. No way to check.
  - Unpublished songs by Carroll Perry, early '60s., AFC 1980/001: SR110; RXB 0068; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
    Unpublished songs by Carroll Perry sung here by Clarence? and Elaine Geeler, possibly later recorded by The Chambers Brothers. Taped in Los Angeles, California, early '60s.
  - Interview and songs with Ramon (Spain), AFC 1980/001: SR111; RXB 0069; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Rodger Bryant, Goin to Kentucky and/or Stop the Flow of Coal, AFC 1980/001: SR112; RXB 0070; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Jim Garland, AFC 1980/001: SR113; RXB 0071; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
    Jim Garland, "Sad Little Land of Vietnam," (partial) Oscar Brand, "A Very Nice Country," 2 takes, not used.
  - Florie-Greek Protest, AFC 1980/001: SR114; RXB 0072; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Greece, Kaimos, AFC 1980/001: SR115; RXB 0073; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - American G.I. talks about the army and the war, AFC 1980/001: SR116; RXB 0074; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Songs about war in Vietnam in Spanish, AFC 1980/001: SR117; RXB 0075; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Soldiers at UFO, Ft. Jackson, AFC 1980/001: SR118; RXB 0076; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Bill Horowitz, Tanya and Rosemary Wood, AFC 1980/001: SR119; RXB 0077; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
    Bill Horowitz, Tanya (about Patty Hearst) and Rosemary Wood (the women who erased Nixon tapes).
  - Chris Rohmann, AFC 1980/001: SR120; RXB 0078; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
    List of songs on bottom of tape box.
  - German protest song from a radio broadcast by David Berger, New York, AFC 1980/001: SR121; RXB 0079; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - "Anti-war songs, Australia", AFC 1980/001: SR122; RXB 0080; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    List of songs on top of tape box.
  - "Mable Hillery (Portelli)", AFC 1980/001: SR123; RXB 0081; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Jack Elliot, Diesel Truck, AFC 1980/001: SR124; RXB 0082; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Lucha, "Sing of Vietnam" (Freedom Voices Never Die), AFC 1980/001: SR125; RXB 0083; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Chicago Women's Liberation Rock Band, 1971, AFC 1980/001: SR126; RXB 0084; 1 audiotape reel, 5 in.
  - Interview with Margaret Barry and Michael Gorman, AFC 1980/001: SR127; RXB 0085; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Conrad Lynn, AFC 1980/001: SR128; RXB 0086; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Lynn a black lawyer active in draft resistance cases, gives detailed talks about Vietnam war from black point of view.
  - "Lavender Country", AFC 1980/001: SR129; RXB 0087; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    List of songs on back of tape box
  - The legacy of Malcolm X, AFC 1980/001: SR130; RXB 0088; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    The legacy of Malcolm X The International Scene as viewed by Malcolm X in his last year, Commentary by George Britman.
  - Interview with Willie Dixon, AFC 1980/001: SR131; RXB 0089; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Rose-Redwoods, AFC 1980/001: SR132; RXB 0090; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Rose-Redwoods, contains two songs, "La Lucha Continuara" and "Take Back the Land."
  - "White Roots of Peace", AFC 1980/001: SR133; RXB 0091; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Margaret Barry and Michael Gorman, AFC 1980/001: SR134; RXB 0092; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    List of songs on inside of tape box.
  - Who's Crazy? by Country Diction, AFC 1980/001: SR135; RXB 0093; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Red Shadows, jokes, gone, gone, gone and anything good, AFC 1980/001: SR136; RXB 0094; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Dorie Ellzey, two songs, Don't Shoot Shadows and When We Make it Through, AFC 1980/001: SR137; RXB 0095; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - War on a People, AFC 1980/001: SR138; RXB 0096; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    This tape dramatizes the methods the U.S. is using in its attempt to win a war against the people of Indochina.
  - Red Star Singers, AFC 1980/001: SR139; RXB 0097; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - The Chambers Brothers, AFC 1980/001: SR140; RXB 0098; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - "The Incredible Rocky," part 2, AFC 1980/001: SR141; RXB 0099; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Red Star Singers, AFC 1980/001: SR142; RXB 0100; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Selection of topical songs, late 1969-1970, AFC 1980/001: SR143; RXB 0101; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Selection of topical songs written during late 1969 and 1970 in the USA. List of songs on piece of paper in box.
  - Kandeda Montgomery, AFC 1980/001: SR144; RXB 0102; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Interviews with American deserters in Canada during Vietnam War, part 4 of 4, AFC 1980/001: SR145; RXB 0103; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Will Hoffman, Radio McGill, and Montreal, interviews American deserters in Canada during Vietnam War.
  - Interviews with American deserters in Canada during Vietnam War, part 1 of 4, AFC 1980/001: SR146; RXB 0104; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Interviews with American deserters in Canada during Vietnam War, part 2 of 4, AFC 1980/001: SR147; RXB 0105; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Interviews with American deserters in Canada during Vietnam War, part 3 of 4, AFC 1980/001: SR148; RXB 0106; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Interview with Dr. Truman, AFC 1980/001: SR149; RXB 0107; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - The Incredible Rocky, part 1, AFC 1980/001: SR150; RXB 0108; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Terry Lipscomb, Texas, AFC 1980/001: SR151; RXB 5826; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Tape has extensive notes. See Terry Lipscomb, Texas for related materials.
  - Mable Hillery, AFC 1980/001: SR152; RXB 0110; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Copies from various sources.
  - Stephen Texas Moon Argo, AFC 1980/001: SR153; RXB 0111; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Stephen Texas Moon Argo talks about why he deserted and sings several songs. List of songs on outside cover.
  - Margaret Barry and Michael Gorman interview, AFC 1980/001: SR154; RXB 0112; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Interview with blues sing Jimmy Witherspoon, part 1 of 2, AFC 1980/001: SR155; RXB 0113; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Barbara‘s Blues radio show from KPFK, Pacifica Station in LA, interview with blues sing Jimmy Witherspoon, with music from selected records. Part 1 of 2.
  - The Poor People's March, AFC 1980/001: SR156; RXB 0114; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
    Tapes made on the way to, and during the Poor People's March.
  - The Poor People's March, AFC 1980/001: SR157; RXB 0115; 1 audiotape reel, 7 in.
  - Unidentified, AFC 1980/001: SR158; RWC 6441; 1 audiotape reel, 10 in.